♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[in English] Oh, I like your office.
- [Dmitri, in English] Very nice.
- [Viktor, in English] My little home.
[in English] Audrey,
what are you doing there?
[Mongki] We're sending
a few more girls this time.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I'm leaving the group.
Are you out of your mind?
[in English] Why do you have
a hole in your window?
[man, in English] The Sokolov brothers
who attended the summit are imposters.
[Samir, in English] I knew it.
We have been compromised.
[grunts]
[in English] Ambassador!
[Paldo] Where's the gang hanging out?
Call them. Drinks are on me!
PREVIOUSLY
[Paldo] I've left the group.
I can't take what they're doing anymore.
[Samir, in English] Check the perimeter.
[in English] We have a breach.
[in English] I repeat, we have
a security breach! Check the perimeter!
[grunting and groaning]
[Viktor, in English]
Did you catch the thief?
[Samir, in English] No.
[in English] I can help you find this man.
[Dmitri, in English] I know
a very good tracker, a man hunter.
I hope you got what you needed to take.
[Paldo] Someone's going
to kill me, Emerson!
- Do you understand?!
- Who?
There! Them!
[Emerson] I'll take care of it.
I'll save you.
Buckle up! Buckle up and duck!
- Duck!
- [multiple gunfire]
[Dmitri] Maybe Atoy can help us.
[in English] Since he's a tracker.
[Audrey, in English] I don't think so.
[music fades]
[Emerson laughs]
How's that, Paldo, huh?
You owe me one.
I want unlimited pares for life.
[foreboding music playing]
Emerson, think about the pares later.
[Paldo] They're right behind us! Hurry up!
- [energetic rock music playing]
- [gunshot]
- [Paldo] Faster!
- [Emerson gasps]
Wait. What's that? An atomic bomb?
That's not an atomic bomb.
That's a bazooka!
Move, or we'll be gone in a flash!
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
It's Atoy. Wait, he's calling. Hold on.
Doesn't Atoy have a gun here, Emerson?
Wait, wait, wait.
I'll ask, I'll ask. Be quiet!
[music fades]
[Emerson] Atoy, Atoy.
- [Atoy] Emerson!
- [Emerson] Help us.
[Atoy] Emerson, where are you?
We're near the extension of…
Wait, don't be noisy!
No, we're at the extension
- near Sampaguita! Huh?
- [Paldo] Hold on to this!
Oh, okay, okay, okay! I'll come to you!
- Hurry!
- Wait, I can't--
- [tense music playing]
- I don't know how to--
Atoy-- Go ahead.
[gun clicks]
[music swells]
It's just like this.
I don't know how to use this, wait!
You can do it!
[action music playing]
[tires screeching]
- [grunts]
- [tires screeching]
[Paldo] Stop.
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
‪[Emerson sighs]
‪[Emerson breathing heavily]
[breathing heavily]
I don't want to. I don't want to.
- I don't want to.
- Are you okay?
No! I don't want to.
I don't want to. I don't want to.
I don't--
[breathing heavily]
[pensive music playing]
Cita] Delfin said
when you were still a kid…
[sighs]
…you were a good kid,
and he was sure you'd grow up
to be a good person.
Really?
Mmm, it's just that
you often hung out with the friends,
but… you've changed too, right?
And if Delfin were alive today,
I'm sure he'd be proud of you.
[Emerson breathing heavily]
[Emerson grunts]
[Emerson] Start up!
Start up. I'm not ready to die yet!
[moaning]
[Emerson grunts]
Emerson, they're almost here.
‪[panting]
‪You must leave now.
- Huh?
- I'll cover you.
No, no! We're not leaving here--
We're not leaving here. I'll help you!
We'll both get out of here alive!
- [somber music playing]
- [heavy breathing]
- [grunting]
- [engine cranking]
[panting]
- Let's go.
- There they are. Come on.
Let's go.
- [action music playing]
- [gasps]
[tires screeching]
[Emerson] What did you do to Mongki?
Why won't he stop hounding you?!
[action music playing]
‪[gasping]
My God! They're here!
Lord, take them already, please!
[Paldo] Emerson!
- Just leave me!
- No, no!
[Emerson] We're both getting out of here!
‪[Emerson grunts]
Emerson, you need
to make sure you survive!
You need to tell Atoy the truth!
What truth?!
[groans]
- [Paldo grunts]
- Paldo!
[Emerson] Paldo.
[energetic rock music playing]
‪Move.
[man] Move!
‪[grunts]
‪Paldo..
[Emerson] Paldo.
[grunts] Son of a thread!
What happened to you guys?
Atoy, I missed you.
This, this is what happened!
[in English] Cover. Cover fire.
- What? What is that?
- Shoot them!
[Emerson gasping]
- [Emerson grunts]
- [Atoy mutters]
‪[grunts, panting]
[groans]
What did you do to Mongki?
Why is he chasing you, huh?
- [Paldo] Atoy, you should leave now!
- [Emerson grunts]
Leave me. Go on!
[Atoy] Hey! What the hell?!
Are you going crazy?
- [Paldo groans]
- [Atoy] Paldo!
What is your problem!?
What's happening to you?
- You need to know something.
- [Emerson gasps]
[Emerson panting] Atoy, they're here!
- It's about your father.
- [Emerson gasps]
- [music fades]
- [heavy breathing]
[sauve theme music playing]
What about my father?
- [sighs]
- [Atoy] Paldo.
I was inside the vehicle.
But I couldn't do anything.
[sobs] Nothing, I couldn't do anything.
[sobbing] I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't save your dad.
[heavy breathing]
- [somber music playing]
- Atoy, forgive me.
What are you saying?
[car revving, tires screeching]
[crashes]
[groans]
[epic music playing]
What are you saying?!
The day your dad got hit-and-run…
you were really his target
because you compromised
the shipment at the port.
But I didn't-- [sobs]
I couldn't do anything to stop it.
[sobbing]
[sighs]
You ran over my dad?
It wasn't me.
- Who did it?
- [heavy breathing]
- Not me.
- [Atoy] Who?
Red.
[music fades]
Red Regalia was the one who hit your dad.
[dramatic music playing]
He… He's the one
who killed your dad, not me, Atoy!
[Paldo groans, heavy breathing]
I'm almost out of bullets, Atoy.
‪[gasps]
Here, eat this! [grunts]
- [ominous music playing]
- [Atoy grunts]
[shouts]
‪[grunts]
Atoy, you should leave now.
I'll handle this!
- Go on!
- [Mongki] Let's go, let's go!
‪[guns cocking]
I'm not done with you yet.
'Son, let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
This will be my karma if I die.
- Come on!
- [Paldo] Go on, get out of here!
Emerson, go now!
Paldo.
[music fades]
- [man] I'll do that.
- I'll take care of it, sis.
- [Denden] You stay there.
- [Mona] That's enough.
[Denden] So, we can still be quick.
Oh, Karla! Hey, come with us!
- We're going to hang out with the gays!
- [giggling]
[girls, in English] Oh my God!
- [Denden, in English] My God!
- [Jona] But wait, Denden.
Karla doesn't go to bars.
If it were basketball, however,
that's a definite yes.
Oh, right. Yes.
Um, okay.
- I'm coming.
- [Jona] Oh!
- [sneaky music playing]
- I don't want to go home yet.
You can definitely join, of course.
But that's a bar.
[Mona] There will be drinking, tugs-tugs!
- And cute boys, of course!
- [giggling]
That's what matters!
But do you have an outfit?
‪[quirky sting]
- Just this.
- That's it?
Oh my, Karla, it's giving
water vendor on the corner vibes.
It can't be like that!
[Mona] That's why.
I have a lot of clothes.
Come with us,
then we'll give you a makeover!
[Mona] Oh, there,
Denden will take care of you.
- [Mona] What?
- [Denden] I got you.
- Let's just help her out.
- Okay, okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go?
- Uncle.
- We'll go ahead.
- [Kurt] Huh? Oh, okay, okay.
- [Mona, in English] Bye!
- Take care, okay?
- [Jona] They'll take care of you.
- [Mona] Mmm-mmm.
- Let's go!
[Denden] Let's help-- Let's help now.
‪-[heavy breathing]
‪-[dramatic sting]
[rousing music playing]
[police siren wailing]
Let's go. Let's go, go, go!
[music swells]
‪[dramatic sting]
Red Regalia was the one
who ran over your dad!
‪[dramatic stinging]
[Atoy] This is what I'll do
to the person who ran over my dad.
[Mongki] Boss, Paldo escaped.
Well, what's new with that?
There were two men who helped him.
But I saw the vehicle they used.
I didn't see Atoy,
but the vehicle they used belongs to Atoy!
And you still didn't catch him?
No, boss.
But this has a connection to Atoy.
Why don't we just go back for Atoy?
I have a feeling
that Paldo is really a spy!
[pensive music playing]
No.
We should've been caught by Atoy
if that were the case.
Let's not touch him for now.
His time will come.
Where does Paldo live?
Let's pay him a visit.
[music fades]
[in English] This is unacceptable!
[Viktor, in English] Whoever attacked me
and stole from my office
is an enemy of our country,
and whoever is connected with him
is also an enemy of our country.
[in English] They will pay.
[in English] We will find you.
[news reporter] According to authorities,
the suspect was able to enter and exit
through a small hole
on the ninth floor of the building.
The investigation continues
on how the suspect
managed to get through
despite the tight security--
[in English] Oh my gosh, Dad.
[in English] Good thing you're okay!
That thief is evil!
[scoffs] Wait, Martina.
We still don't know-- Uh--
What if they're the bad ones?
They're the ones who were robbed,
and yet they're the bad ones too?
[in English] No, okay.
What I'm trying to say is…
we don't know why they took
the laptop from the embassy office.
Maybe there's evidence there
about his shady deals.
[in English] I've heard rumors
about the ambassador.
[in English] That he supports genocide
in conflict countries.
[in English] Come on, Audrey.
[in English] Dad,
you should really rethink
doing business with the ambassador.
[in English] Audrey,
those are just rumors.
[in English] I agree with Martina.
The bad guy, the guy who stole,
he even hurt me.
[sinister music playing]
[in English] But that's only
because he was trying to escape.
[in English] You weren't his target.
He didn't hurt me, Dad.
You know,
it sounds like
you're the thief's accomplice.
You're defending him so much.
Are you two close?
[in English] What?
No! Ah-- How are we supposed to be close?
I don't know him!
[in English] It's a joke, Audrey.
[in English] Stop being
so serious all the time.
[rousing music playing]
- [Emerson] 'Toy, 'Toy. W-wait, wait.
- [Ame] Hey!
- [Atoy] Move, move!
- [Ame] What happened to you guys?
What's your plan? [panting]
I'm going to kill them.
- Atoy. Wait, 'Toy.
- I'm going to kill that Red.
Cal-- Calm down first, 'Toy.
Your rage is clouding your decision!
How am I supposed to calm down?!
All this time, we've been interacting
with the people who killed my father!
[Atoy] And Paldo?
He knew all this time!
Why did he just tell me now?
I understand. Okay, okay.
Let all your anger out.
But remember, you are not a murderer.
If you want to retaliate,
do it it through legal means!
Isn't that what you taught me?
- [in English] Legal?!
- Yes! Let's involve the police then!
The police?! There is nothing
the police can do!
They got away with it before, more so now.
We don't have any evidence!
And they're going to kill Paldo!
[tense music playing]
There is no legal way
for demons like that!
- [Emerson] ‘Toy.
- [Ame] Hey!
[intense music playing]
Emerson, please stop Atoy!
We don't know what he might do.
How can I stop him?
Do you want me to get killed by him too?
[music swells]
[man] Paldo?
Paldo!
Here. That's Captain's house over there.
- [Red] Thank you.
- All right.
[ominous music playing]
Are you also looking for Paldo?
I've been calling him,
but no one's answering.
[guns cocking]
[tense music playing]
- [lively chattering]
- [elated shrieking]
Here we are! Just in time!
[exclaims]
[in English] Barangay Tabang Lupa
beauties coming at ya!
- [in English] Hello!
- [elated shrieking]
- Hey, wait. Where's Karla?
- [Mona] Karla?
- Yes.
- She was just here earlier.
[Jona] Karla? Is that Karla?
[Jona and Mona] Oh!
[Mona] Karla.
[Denden] Why the frown?
Smile! Show off!
[exclaiming]
I'm just not used to this.
I just wanted to drink.
Karla, come on.
You won't get in
if you're wearing
basketball shorts and a T-shirt.
- [Mona] Yes.
- So, it's fine, just go for it.
[in English] Let's go!
[lively chatter]
- [Mona] Take it slow.
- We're gonna enjoy tonight.
[lively chattering]
[Denden] Just smile, smile!
‪[Jona gasps]
‪-[indistinct chattering]
‪-[inaudible]
[Denden] Hey! I'm gonna eat-and-run.
- [Jona] So, what now?
- [Mona] Go, order.
[Jona] Denden, treat us.
Wow, that's six months to pay off, huh.
- Pay for your drinks.
- Drinks!
- [in English] Thank you, baby, okay.
- Oh, wow.
[Denden] Your 'babies'
are all over the place, huh?
[Jona] But to brother, that's a baby. Oh!
- [Jona] Here it comes!
- [in English] Cheers!
- [shrieking]
I'll have water first.
[lively chattering]
Let's order some pares.
[Denden] Oh, okay.
Ah, babe, let's just stay here.
I'll just order drinks at the bar,
okay, because…
there's no waiter. Have a seat.
Okay, babe. Thanks!
This is where we're sitting.
[in English] Oh, wait.
[in English] Is that Karla?
- [magical twinkle]
- [romantic music playing]
It is her.
This is the first time
I'm seeing her like that.
[in English] She's trying way too hard.
Her overall look is so cheap.
The outfit is kinda gross.
[in English] I know, right?
Like, what on earth is she wearing?
You know, Karla's actually nice.
Don't laugh at her.
♪ It's not that Im thinking bad thoughts ♪
[music fades]
[Ibyang] If Sister Karla
isn't on the basketball court,
then, where could she possibly be?
I honestly don't know.
Let's just go back to the tailoring shop.
Maybe Atoy is there.
Let's ask for help to find her.
[Cita] Oh, Ibyang, why?
- Miss Cita, you go on ahead.
- [melancholic music playing]
I'll just go home.
Ibyang, are you still sulking? Jeez.
Atoy always asks me about you.
He's sad that you're ignoring him.
He just doesn't admit it,
but he really loves you.
That's not true.
You're just saying that.
Huh? It's true!
[car revving]
[shouts] Ibyang!
[Cita] Help me! Help!
Ibyang, Ibyang!
Help!
Ibyang! Ibyang--
- Help, help.
- [tense music playing]
[Cita] Let's carry her.
Help.
Karla, we're stepping out for a bit.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Just stay here, okay?
- We'll be back.
- Just stay there.
- Oh, okay.
- [Mona] Promise, okay.
[Denden] Don't move.
- Yes. Okay.
- [Jona] Just dance.
- [Denden] Don't leave.
- [Mona] We'll be back.
[lively chattering]
[Denden] Just smile, smile.
Karla, take it slow.
Gavin, hello! You're here too?
When did you learn to drink?
This?
This isn't alcohol. It's just a mocktail.
I don't drink.
And also, why are you dressed like that?
Why are you hanging out here?
You know, those sudden changes
indicate you have a problem.
You can just tell me, you know.
Well, you're always busy.
And besides, my problem is really tough.
You wouldn't understand it.
Because you're a rich kid.
You can't relate.
[in English] Try me.
[Cathy] Uh, Karla!
[in English] Wait!
[in English] You look so, uh, cute!
[Cathy chuckles]
[in English] Do you want
to join us at the table?
You poor thing, sitting there all alone.
No, it's okay. I'm with Sis Denden.
- Who…?
- [Karla] Denden.
- [pensive music playing]
- Where are they? [chuckles]
[Cathy] Come on. Don't be shy.
[in English] Come on.
[in English] Come on!
Join our table. We're just there.
Come on. Let's go.
[in English] Let's go!
We'll just stay here.
Here, have a seat.
Uh, waiter.
[suspicious music playing]
One Amaretto Sour for him.
'Toy, ah-- What are you gonna do?
Emerson, get out of my way.
'Toy, hmm-- Let's just drink!
Let's just drink!
- 'Toy, wait-- Ah--
- Emerson!
Ame, Ame, help me out.
- Stand here and block him!
- [Atoy] Ame.
As if my blocking will do anything.
He'll just step over me.
'Toy, 'Toy, think
about what you'll do first.
- [Ame] Atoy.
- [Emerson, in English] Please?
Ah, bro, you want to drink now.
I'll buy some ice!
- [Atoy] Move aside!
- [both] Atoy!
[T-Bak] Brother Atoy! [sighs]
There are men outside
Paldo's house.
Then they shot at his house!
- [Emerson] Huh?
- They are the same men who came before.
They were looking for you too!
Mongki and the others.
Maybe Red is with them.
They're gone! Those guys are gone!
- Those guys are gone.
- Oh, yes!
- Maybe?
- What the heck is that about?!
- Move!
- [Emerson] 'Toy, 'Toy, 'Toy, 'Toy!
- Think about this first, Atoy--
- [Munggo] Atoy, Atoy!
It's Ibyang!
[Munggo] She was taken to the hospital!
- She almost got hit earlier!
- [Ame] Huh?
[intense music playing]
Karla, don't you drink?
No, not really.
[Cathy] Come on, just try it!
[cool upbeat music playing]
Babe, she doesn't want to.
Don't force her.
[in English] Okay, fine.
- Are you having fun at least?
- [in English] Yes.
- [Cathy] Hmm? Really?
- Yes.
Doesn't seem like it!
[in English] Come on! Let's have fun!
[in English] Gavin, come on.
Let's dance. Let's dance!
[Cathy giggles]
[in English] Come on! Karla!
[in English] I dare you to…
dance on top of the chair.
- [in English] Babe.
- [Cathy, in English] Come on!
Karla! Karla! Karla! Karla! Karla!
[Cathy] Go ahead!
[Cathy whoops and chuckles]
- [Gavin] Karla, just take it slow, okay?
- [in English] Go!
- [whoops]
- [Cathy, in English] More! Let's go.
[in English] Dance-off!
- [in English] Let's go!
- [in English] Yes!
Go! Keep going! [whoops, chuckles]
[Gavin] Karla, stop.
- You might get hurt.
- [Karla] No, it's okay.
- [Gavin] Karla, come down, come down.
- [Cathy, in English] Come on, Karla!
[in English] Babe, stop doing this to her.
You're making fun of her.
[in English] Gavin,
we're having fun with her!
Karla, where are your friends anyway?
Sis Denden and the others?
They might have gone back already.
Ah, I'll just go find them.
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
We saw you dancing earlier.
- Let's dance there.
- Is that okay?
Come join us.
[suspicious music playing]
[ambulance siren wailing]
Uh…
Miss Cita already talked to the doctor.
[Emerson] They said
Ibyang's CT scan result is okay, so…
she's ready for discharge.
Miss Cita is at the cashier now.
Thanks.
[melancholic music playing]
Where am I?
Ibyang.
[Atoy] You're at the hospital.
‪[inhales]
The vehicle sideswiped you.
You got hit.
You fell pretty hard.
Do you remember
what kind of vehicle it was?
Well…
The vehicle was moving quickly.
Exactly. [clicks tongue]
My God, Ibyang.
Next time, be careful, okay?
Watch where you're going.
When you step out
on the road, look around.
All the passing vehicles,
any one of them can hit you.
And you're still so little!
Are you mad at me?
No!
The same thing happened to my father.
But he died. Fortunately you…
You did not.
I don't want that to happen again, okay?
Because I don't want
to lose someone I love.
Do you still love me, even if
I'm upset with you?
Even if you don't like me. [chuckles]
Yes, I love you.
[sentimental music playing]
Let's make up now.
Oh, it's just you who's mad at me, anyway.
It's just you, really.
[scoffs]
[nurse] Sir, I just need
to check the patient.
Don't take this the wrong way, Atoy.
It's not that…
I'm glad that something
happened to Ibyang.
But if we think about it, it's kind of…
a blessing in disguise too.
Because she stopped you.
[pensive music playing]
Think about it.
Had you rushed to confront Red earlier,
you'd have been at a disadvantage.
There are too many of them.
You probably would have been killed there.
You're not allowed to die, right?
He's lucky
because he'll still make it
until tomorrow.
[rousing music playing]
‪[electronic blipping]
[Atoy] You have
lots of other friends, right?
UP NEXT
I want you to stay away from Karla.
I don't have any bad intentions
towards Karla.
Believe me. This will be better for her.
The Sister Norma who suddenly disappeared?
[Mongki] My guy found out
she moved to the province
and then went to Manila.
Have you found her already?
[henchman] Hey!
What are you doing here?!
- [groaning]
- Hey!
[grunting and groaning]
- [thumping]
- [gunfire]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias